CURRICULUM VITAE

SANJEEV KUMAR RAJPUT

Permanent Address:

Post Address:

H.no.B I 665/9B New Upkar Nagar Civil Lines Ludhiana., Ph:-09814905447 H.No.B I 665/9B New Upkar Nagar Civil Lines Ludhiana., Ph:-09814905447

Objective

To realize my full potential in an organization that appreciates hard work and believes in organizational and employee development s

THE CAREER THAT I SEEK

What I seek in a career is a challenge at every step, a catalyst for my passion to achieve targets and a chance to hone my acquired skills through learning and experience, an organization that values innovation and hard work would bring out the best in me.

Work Experience: -

Distt Courts Ludhiana:- Worked as advocate for four year with Sh Sukhpat Rai Wadehra Sen most Advocate and Alok Mohindra advocate(empaneled lawyer with ICICI bank, Kotak Mahindra, SBOP, L I C ETC) for 7 Years (From January 2001 to July 2007).

At present (Feb 2013 till now) working as AM Legal Ludhiana, Patiala , Fatehgarh, Saheb , Moga, Jalandhar, Kapurthala, AmritSar, tarantarn, Hoshiarpur, SSS Nagar Himachal locations and Chandigarh location Magma Fincorp Ltd at base Ludhiana Location

Work profile –Filing and following of Arbitration Executions, Sec 138 of N I Act and handling of Against cases, Consumer and Civil Etc. and Oracle Updation

Execution of sec 9 order, Sec 17 of arbitration award and Sarfeasi with vernacular of docs and from 13.2 to till the possession a to z.

Handling Police complaints By and Against Us.

Chola Mandlam Finance and Investment LTD Ludhiana and Jalandhar:-2011 to 2013 Working as Sr. Legal Executive in PL and Mainly Auto and CV Legal.

ICICI Bank Limited:- 2007 to 2011 Worked as a Legal Co-Coordinator in STPL, PL, AUTO AND TW Legal and Collection, Ludhiana.

Key Responsibilities:-

- Handling Collection Agency 90 Dpd
- Proceeding the Legals.
- Coordination with Empaneled Lawyer.
- Maintaining MIS Report.
- Daily maintenance of bouncing Cheques detail and sending legal notices u/s 13

- Maintaining Case Filing U/S Sec-138, Sec 9 of Arbitration act, Permission to sale, Consumer forum cases and legal reply in complaint cases and OMBUDSMAN<or RBI complaint cases, and u/s 156 complaint cases.
- Civil recovery cases, Demand Legals Notices sent as routine wise before cycle date (bkt 4,5,6 in flows allocation), Lok Adalat cases.
- Proceeding the Summons, Warrants in Bank Cases, Conciliation Notices, Legal Notices U/S 138, Arbitration cases. Execution of Sec 9 Receiver order of Arbitration Act with ACP Traffic.
- Updated Legal Trail in Company Software

Educational Profile

Level	Institute	Board/University	
Matric	Punjab School Education Board	PSEB1990	
10+2	Punjab School Education Board PSEB1992		
Bachelor of Arts	Punjab University, Chandigarh PUCH1995		
M.A. (Pol Sci)	Punjab University, Chandigarh PUCH1997		
L.L.B	Shree Ganga Nagar Collage Ajmer University (Raj)	Ajmer University (Raj)	
Computer Basic	Chandigarh Computer Center	Private Institute	

Strength

- Hard working.
- Creative Thinking.
- Completely responsible for productivity targets.
- Continuous monitoring & development of new system.
- Achievement oriented with excellent people management skills.
- Interaction with people from divisive environments and dialects.
- Working in Highly competitive environment.
- Excellent negotiation and analysis skills.
- Capable of working in team under pressure to get best out of me..
- Always willing to learn.

Language Proficiency

	English	Hindi	Punjabi
Read			
Write			
Speak			

Personal Details

Father's Name : Sh. Darshan Kumar Rajput

Date of Birth :08th Sep. 1974 Contact No. :09814905447

Nationality :Indian
Gender :Male
Marital status :Married

Sanjeev Kumar Rajput Ludhiana. DT 17-3-22